Contact

chieutrangg@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/trangphan-443744194 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Marketing
User Experience (UX)
Front-end Development

Languages

Vietnamese English

Certifications

Digital Garage Certificate

Honors-Awards

Athletics

Trang Phan

Actively looking for a job Vaasa

Summary

Experienced customer service executive with a demonstrated history of working in the marketing and advertising industry. Skilled in Marketing, Digital Marketing, Photography, Advertising, and Public Relations. Strong operations professional with a Bachelor's degree focused on International Business from Vaasan ammattikorkeakoulu VAMK University of Applied Sciences.

Experience

Wapice Ltd IoT hackathon March 2021 - March 2021 (1 month) Vaasa, Ostrobothnia, Finland

Gather a team (4-5 people) and register for a hackathon organized by Wapice. The event held in March 2021 as a remote event. During the hackathon, the team will get to know Wapice's IoT-TICKET® product and complete the challenge. Teams have three weeks to create IoT applications.

Slush Slush 2019 November 2019 - November 2019 (1 month) Helsinki Area, Finland

Slush Helsinki is the most founder-focused event on earth. 25,000 changemakers, including 4,000 startups and scaleups, and 2,000 investors.

Vegoshi
Customer Service Executive
December 2018 - October 2019 (11 months)
Vaasa Area, Finland

Part-time work, sale.

Junction Ltd Tech Race Finland 2019 September 2019 - September 2019 (1 month) Vaasa Area, Finland

Tech Race events are one-night-events designed for everyone interested in tech and hackathons. The challenges vary in difficulty, so you will definitely be able to solve some of the challenges but definitely not all of them.

Tech Race Finland tours through cities of Finland trying to find the top concentration of tech masterminds in our country. In every event, the local participants will receive a large pool of challenges to solve, ranging from programming puzzles to design problems, from basic tasks to extremely tricky ones.

Experienced:

- Learning new skills
- Solving new problems
- Meeting new people
- Having FUN

KLong Marketing Intern April 2019 - August 2019 (5 months)

Vietnam

Taking part in Research and Development in package, product and service department and also in marketing realm internship in KLong Co., LTD, me and my team

(5 people including me) responsible for a strategy project in R&D and marketing:

Research information, create a special package for product and content to prepare

for Full-moon festival (Mid-autumn festival) and back to school event content.

Education

Vaasan ammattikorkeakoulu VAMK University of Applied Sciences Bachelor's degree, International Business · (2017 - 2020)

Chu Van An National High School High School Diploma (2013 - 2016)